{"_quizName": "Unit Conversions-Introductory", "quiz": {"questions": [{"prompt": "The length of the playground is 100 yards.  What is the length in feet?(1yard=3feet)", "choices": [{"correct": false, "value": "100ft"}, {"correct": false, "value": "30ft"}, {"correct": false, "value": "200ft"}, {"correct": true, "value": "300ft"}]}, {"prompt": "Miguel kicked the soccer ball 12 meters.  How many centimeters did he kick the soccer ball?(1cm=0.01m)", "choices": [{"correct": true, "value": "1200cm"}, {"correct": false, "value": "120cm"}, {"correct": false, "value": "12000cm"}, {"correct": false, "value": "1000cm"}]}, {"prompt": "The length of the playground is 100 yards.  What is the length in feet?(1yard=3feet)", "choices": [{"correct": false, "value": "100ft"}, {"correct": false, "value": "30ft"}, {"correct": false, "value": "200ft"}, {"correct": true, "value": "300ft"}]}, {"prompt": "1 liter is:", "choices": [{"correct": true, "value": "1000ml"}, {"correct": false, "value": "100ml"}, {"correct": false, "value": "10ml"}, {"correct": false, "value": "1ml"}]}, {"prompt": "What is the metric unit for volume?", "choices": [{"correct": true, "value": "litre"}, {"correct": false, "value": "metre"}, {"correct": false, "value": "gram"}, {"correct": false, "value": "kelvin"}]}, {"prompt": "The number 535.602 rounded to 3 significant figures is:", "choices": [{"correct": false, "value": "535,6"}, {"correct": false, "value": "535"}, {"correct": true, "value": "536"}, {"correct": false, "value": "0.602"}]}, {"prompt": "When converting 7,000 nA to microamperes, the result is", "choices": [{"correct": false, "value": "0.007"}, {"correct": false, "value": "0.7"}, {"correct": false, "value": "700"}, {"correct": true, "value": "7"}]}, {"prompt": "Express 3,124 centimeters in meters.", "choices": [{"correct": true, "value": "31.24"}, {"correct": false, "value": "32"}, {"correct": false, "value": "31"}, {"correct": false, "value": "33"}]}, {"prompt": "Intensity of electric current is expressed in", "choices": [{"correct": false, "value": "volts"}, {"correct": false, "value": "watts"}, {"correct": true, "value": "amperes"}, {"correct": false, "value": "joules"}]}, {"prompt": "In the SI system, the basic unit of measurement for mass is the:", "choices": [{"correct": true, "value": "kilogram."}, {"correct": false, "value": "metres"}, {"correct": false, "value": "kilometres"}, {"correct": false, "value": "joules"}]}]}}